Did you know training a single LLM can emit as much carbon as five cars over their entire lifetimes?
Meet EcoCompute AI, the first "Green AI" Architect powered by Gemini 3 Pro.
It’s not just a linter. It’s a virtual Performance Engineer that sees your architecture—literally.
You can paste your PyTorch code or even upload a hand-drawn sketch of your neural network.
Gemini 3 analyzes the visual topology to detect hidden bottlenecks that static analysis might miss.
But we don't just guess. EcoCompute uses Gemini's Agentic capabilities to ground every decision.
Watch as it uses Google Search to pull real-time 2026 hardware specs, like the latest NVIDIA B200 TDPs.
Then, it uses the Code Execution tool to write and run Python scripts in a sandbox, verifying Arithmetic Intensity math.
The result? A comprehensive "Deep Energy Audit" with a structured breakdown of Joules and Carbon.
Check out the "Decision Triangle." It forces you to balance Performance, Cost, and Carbon Efficiency.
It doesn't just complain; it fixes. Here, Gemini auto-refactors the code, applying quantization and LoRA optimizations.
Under the hood, we built a "Hybrid Grounding System." We combine deterministic AST analysis with probabilistic LLM reasoning.
We even cross-reference predictions against the MLPerf Inference v4.1 database for ground-truth accuracy.
The "Thinking Panel" shows you exactly how the model reasons, planning its search queries and calculations step-by-step.
With EcoCompute AI, developers can reduce their model's energy consumption by 30 to 50 percent.
Sustainable AI isn't just a goal; it's a responsibility. Join us in democratizing Green AI expertise.
EcoCompute AI. Let's Code Green.
[EcoCompute AI - Powered by Gemini 3]